Guide to the Willis Grant Johnson papers, 1901-1904.
Johnson, Willis Grant papers, 1901-1904
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Willis Grant Johnson papers, 1901-1904.
21-02-471
Willis Grant Johnson, 1866-1908.
.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, printed matter, and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, printed matter, and photographs concerning efforts to obtain funds from the state legislature for the construction of agricultural college buildings at Cornell University. The principal correspondents are Liberty Hyde Bailey, John Craig, George Malby, Isaac Phillips Roberts, Jacob Gould Schurman, John Spencer, Edwin Stewart, John Lemuel Stone, Henry Hiram Wing, and Daniel Parrish Witter.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Willis Grant Johnson was editor of the American Agriculturist.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, printed matter, and photographs concerning efforts to obtain funds from the state legislature for the construction of agricultural college buildings at Cornell University. Most of the correspondence is that of Willis Grant Johnson; it indicates Johnson's part in obtaining funding. The principal correspondents are Liberty Hyde Bailey, John Craig, George Malby, Isaac Phillips Roberts, Jacob Gould Schurman, John Spencer, Edwin Stewart, John Lemuel Stone, Henry Hiram Wing, and Daniel Parrish Witter.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Johnson, Willis Grant, 1866-1908.; Bailey, L. H. (Liberty Hyde), 1858-1954.; Craig, John, 1864-1912.; Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1833-1928.; Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1854-1942.; New York State College of Agriculture--Buildings.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Oct.-Nov. 1901 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dec. 1-19, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dec. 20-31, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Jan.-Feb. 1902 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mar. 1902 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Nov.-Dec. 1902 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Jan.-Feb. 1903 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mar.-May 1903 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1904 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Photographed (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Printed matter (Box 1, Folder 13)